<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Cottage Painter</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Cottage Painter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://cottagepainter.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/myself/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/myself/</guid><description>My name is Currie Carmichael, I&amp;rsquo;m a professional painter who&amp;rsquo;s been serving the islands between Parry Sound and Moon River since 2016. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a cottager in the area my entire life and am prepared, equipped, and ready to handle any project on the Bay.
My season generally lasts from mid-May until the end of September.
I offer, for every service, a firm, quoted price. I believe this is the fairest structure for both parties.</description></item><item><title>Exterior Painting</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/exterior-painting/</guid><description>I offer modern, efficient, large-scale exterior painting. Modern; I use the most modern equipment and tools as the basis of my process. Efficient; my process is effective and practiced. Large-scale; my process can handle any size job on the Bay.
Process Estimation Washing Preparation Application Cleanup Estimation I require two numbers:
The days it will take to complete the job The gallons of paint required I don&amp;rsquo;t do any fancy measurements to figure them out, just my own gut-feeling tempered with experience.</description></item><item><title>Gutter Cleaning</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/services/gutter-cleaning/</guid><description>Using a high-pressure pressure washer, an extension wand, and a special attachment, I am able to wash-out your eavestroughs without ever having to climb a ladder. Fast, efficient, and highly effective.
NOTE: Currently this service is only offered as an add-on to my other services.</description></item><item><title>Insurance</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/insurance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/insurance/</guid><description>Cottage Painter is fully insured by Lloyd&amp;rsquo;s through Martin Merry &amp;amp; Reid Limited.
#the-canvas { border: 1px solid #212121; direction: ltr; width: 100%; height: auto; } #paginator{ text-align: center; margin-bottom: 10px; } Download Copy 🡄 🡆 Page: / window.onload = function() { var url = "\/pdf\/insurance-redacted.pdf"; var pdfjsLib = window['pdfjs-dist/build/pdf']; pdfjsLib.GlobalWorkerOptions.workerSrc = "\/js\/pdf-js\/build\/pdf.worker.js"; var pdfDoc = null, pageNum = 1, pageRendering = false, pageNumPending = null, scale = 3, canvas = document.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/about/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>Definitions The pronoun I, and all other references to the first-person, refer to Currie Carmichael, the Cottage Painter, as well as any of my employees The pronoun you, and all other references to the second-person, refer to the client who hired me The Jobsite, as well as terms like Onsite, refers to both the time and place where all contracted work will take place. possibly several locations/timeframes The Timeframe refers to the period of time during which all contracted work will take place possibly discontinuous The Estimate refers to the estimate you have received from Currie Carmichael The Invoice refers to the invoice you have received from Currie Carmichael The Daily Charge referred to the daily charge stated on your copy of the estimate/invoice A Season refers to a year that Cottage Painter was active The Current Season refers to 2022 You Expect That The final price will reflect the estimated price in most cases they are identical The work will be completed in a timely and professional manner You will not be required to provide equipment You will not be required to provide accommodation You will not be required to provide sustenance The jobsite will be left in a clean state when the job is complete The jobsite will be left in a tidy state between work days however, if the jobsite is not being used by anyone else except me, or if tidiness, for whatever reason is unimportant, I may leave the jobsite in a less then tidy state purely for efficiency reasons All disputes will be dealt with in a reasonable and responsible manner I Expect That Docking is available Doors will be left unlocked Electricity will be available Estimates will be updated every season Equipment can be stored onsite Running water is available The jobsite will be ready when I arrive The timeframe will be respected Docking is available There will be a safe place at the jobsite for my boat to dock.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Free Estimate</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/free-estimate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/free-estimate/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hiring</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/hiring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/hiring/</guid><description>Looking for a summer job? Look no further! Join the greatest band of painters ever assembled on Georgian Bayfor an epic, summer-long adventure of:
Backbrushing&amp;hellip; Brush arm and leg through hundreds, potentially thousands of gallons of paint as you struggle to push viscous liquid deep within the cavernous pores of wood Caulking&amp;hellip; Caulk where no man has caulked before; Grab that Caulk and Caulk baby; CAUUULLLLLKKK Masking&amp;hellip; Defend thousands of square-feet of window and deck from the dreaded overspray; block its vain attempts to destroy my reputation Moving&amp;hellip; Pickup things in one location and move them to another location using the magic of the human motor system Painting&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;painting&amp;hellip;?</description></item><item><title>References</title><link>https://cottagepainter.github.io/references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cottagepainter.github.io/references/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>